John Milton Ramm
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Photographs, 1903-1981, undated, Series 7:; (Boxes 8-10, 12, OV 15; 2.4 linear feet)
  - Photographs by John Milton Ramm (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a Rocky Mountain trip, undated (Box 9)
    - Photographs of Oregon, undated, (4 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of Japan (?), undated (Box 9)
    - Unidentified travel photographs, undated, . (4 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of miscellaneous ships, undated (Box 9)
    - Photographs of the fleet under the Golden Gate Bridge, undated (Box 9)
    - Photographs of trip to Monterey, La Honda, and Tamalpais, 1920s (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a Shriner convention, 1922 (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a voyage to Hawaii, 1923, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of Pasadena and Santa Cruz, California, 1923 (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a trip to the California desert, 1923 (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a voyage to New York, Philadelphia, and the Panama Canal, 1924, (4 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a voyage to Hawaii, China, the Philippines, and Japan, 1924, (3 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a trip to Yosemite, 1924, (5 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a voyage to Central America, Cuba, and New York, 1925, (3 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a voyage to West Africa and New York, 1925-1926, (8 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of voyage to New York, Norfolk, and San Francisco, 1926 (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a voyage to Central America, 1926, (9 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a voyage to Israel, Turkey, Greece, and Egypt, 1926-1927, (5 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of Antwerp, Belgium, 1927, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a voyage to South America, 1927 (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a voyage to Australia and Tasmania, 1927-1928, (6 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a voyage to the Celebes, the Philippines, and Hong Kong, 1928, (9 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs of a dirigible, 1929 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of United Artists movie sets in Hollywood, 1929 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of a voyage to Alaska, 1932, (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of a ski trip, 1937 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of opening day of the Golden Gate Bridge, 1937 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of a voyage to Central America and the Panama Canal Zone, 1937-1938, (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of the Golden Gate International Exposition, 1939-1940, (7 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of a trip to Arizona, 1940 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of Monterey, California, 1940 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of Mt. Whitney, California, 1946 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of a voyage to Hawaii and the Philippines, 1946-1947, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of Cliff House, San Francisco, 1948 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of art work by John Milton Ramm (Box 10)
      - "Benson Portraits," undated, (2 folders) (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous café murals, undated, (4 folders) (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous art work, undated, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 10)
  - Photographs by John Henry Ramm (Box 10)
    - Photographs of miscellaneous views of California, undated, (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of downtown San Francisco, undated, (6 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of Telegraph Hill, undated, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of Golden Gate Park,undated, (8 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of miscellaneous parks in San Francisco, undated, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of Berkeley and Palo Alto, undated, (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of waterfront and beach, undated, (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of miscellaneous views of San Francisco, undated (Box 10)
    - Photographs of miscellaneous ships, undated (Box 10)
    - Photographs of a waterfall and of San Francisco, 1903-1905 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of the San Francisco fire and earthquake damage, 1906, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of the Northwest Coast, 1906 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of San Francisco, 1913 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of the eruption of the Mt. Lassen Volcano, 1914 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of San Francisco, 1915-1918 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of a path in the forest, 1919 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of "Old San Francisco," 1924 (Box 10)
    - Photographs of California and Nevada, 1925 (Box 10)
    - Painted photographs, undated, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Photographs of art work by John Henry Ramm, undated, (9 folders) (Box 10)
  - Photographs by others of miscellaneous images, including views of the Gilbert Islands, 1915-1946, undated, (2 folders) (Box 10)
  - Oversize photographs of John Milton Ramm, 1904 (Box 12 (sol))
  - Oversize photographs of John Milton Ramm, 1921 (Box OV 15)
- Printed material, 1913-1963, Series 8:; (Boxes 10-12; 54 folders)
  Printed material includes clippings, an exhibition announcement for John Milton Ramm, miscellaneous calling cards for individuals and businesses, a school yearbook, published scripts, and miscellaneous booklets and programs.
  - Clippings (See Also Box 12), 1913-1963, undated, (24 folders) (Box 10)
  - Exhibition announcement for John Milton Ramm, undated (Box 11 (hol))
  - Calling cards for John Milton Ramm, undated (Box 11 (hol))
  - Calling cards for John Henry Ramm and Mrs. Ramm, undated, (2 folders) (Box 11 (hol))
  - Miscellaneous calling cards, undated (Box 11 (hol))
  - Miscellaneous calling cards (See Also Box 12), undated, (2 folders) (Box 11 (hol))
  - School yearbook The Lowell, 1921 (Box 11 (hol))
  - Script "Double Speed," by J. Stewart Woodhouse, 1920 (Box 11 (hol))
  - Script, "Hail the Woman," by C. Gardner Sullivan, 1921 (Box 11 (hol))
  - Script, "The Man Under Cover," by Louis Victor Eytinge, 1922 (Box 11 (hol))
  - Booklet, "Use and Care of Drawing Instruments," undated (Box 11 (hol))
  - Booklet, "San Francisco Nursery for Homeless Children Annual Report," 1918-1919 (Box 11 (hol))
  - Booklet, "Bleacher Songs and Yells," Lowell High School, 1921 (Box 11 (hol))
  - Miscellaneous programs, 1921-1962, undated, (3 folders) (Box 11 (hol))
  - Miscellaneous menus, undated (Box 11 (hol))
  - Miscellaneous brochures, undated (Box 11 (hol))
  - Hotel advertisement cards, undated (Box 11 (hol))
  - Restaurant advertisement cards, undated (Box 11 (hol))
  - Miscellaneous business cards, undated, (2 folders) (Box 11 (hol))
  - Picture postcards, undated (Box 11 (hol))
  - Blank stationery, undated (Box 11 (hol))
  - Miscellaneous printed material, 1924-1959, (4 folders) (Box 11 (hol))
  - Oversize clippings, 1931 (Box 12 (hol))
  - Oversize reproductions of art work, undated (Box 12 (hol))
- Artifacts, undated, Series 9:; (Box 12; 1 folder)
  - Hand-carved backscratcher, undated (Box 12 (hol))
  - Rubber stamp of a heraldic emblem, undated (Box 12 (hol))